LIES,
>> LIES,
>> LIES. JOSH ALLEN in 2018, Josh Hines
Allen 2019.
>> Cuz now I'm just sitting around
and it's too quiet.
>> Coming up on a Get Loud podcast, we will
talk about the commander's biggest needs
in the draft. Also, this is a new new
podcast.
>> Yes, it is. We're going to talk about
Massachusetts.
>> We're going to talk about Massachusetts.
>> We're also going to have a mini draft of
the best number seven overall picks of
all time. And you'll be shocked who went
numbers and can we make Anna world
famous. Tick tock, tick tock, tick tock.
Welcome inside the Big Bear AI Command
Center Studio. It is the Get Loud
podcast presented by SeatGeek, the
official primary ticketing partner of
Washington Commanders. Find tickets to
Commanders games and more at SegeGeek.
Fred Smoot.
>> What's up, Michael Janky?
>> How you doing, man? How's the weekend,
>> man? I'm good. Listen, we got a 85°ree
weather day.
>> Nice.
>> I took advantage of it. Georgetown
waterfront. It was great. I listen, it's
something about just sitting in that sun
and soaking up them sun rays. It just
give you energy.
>> Yeah.
>> I like I I think we missed that in the
winter time cuz And I like it, you know,
cuz we're from the south and we got
basically winter I mean uh summer,
spring, and spring again. Now here we
got all of these seasons and I enjoy the
rest up in the winter time and kind of
refocus and then bam, here come spring
and it feels good. It does feel good.
>> I should have taken more advantage of it
this weekend. I was kind of indoors but
then I go out late in the afternoon. I
should have taken in more than I'm so
white.
>> Listen and that's the only way to get
that pale off of you.
>> I'm like translucent. Yeah, you're going
to have to get outside, man. And and the
sun, that's something that I always did
when I was young. And my mama thought,
>> he's crazy.
>> I used to do this early every Sunday and
Saturday morning. I used to literally go
outside in the morning and eat my cereal
in the driveway
>> because I wanted You
>> used to eat your cereal in the driveway.
>> I used to eat my neighbors like this
dude is throat. I would get up.
>> Okay. make me a big old bowl of cereal.
>> Yeah.
>> And I would go outside and eat them in
the sun.
>> You know what I love with cereal?
>> Yeah.
>> Warm milk.
>> What?
>> Who does that?
>> Just No. BUT YOU'RE SITTING IN THE SUN.
>> Warm milk all the time, Brad. That's why
we're
>> No. Hot bowl of milk. I know.
>> Give me some of that hot milk of my
>> I wasn't going out there to heat the
milk up. I was going out to take in sun
rays while I ate the cereal of my dream.
Milk's going to be like chunky.
>> I like soggy cereal with really warm
milk.
>> I like sun with my cereal.
>> Okay.
>> That's That's all it was. I liked son
with my cereal. And my mom used to be at
the door just
I think something wrong with him.
Guys, you got to give us a call. Let us
know what you think about Fred eating
cereal in the sun. It's
7037267419737267419.
Of course, like and subscribe, please,
to the Commander YouTube channel. And
you can email us if you want to
Washington Getloud@gmail.com.
Also, we got to keep promoting this.
>> Yeah,
>> your mockdraft challenge. A lot of fans
out there want to take you on.
>> Challenge the draft guru.
>> Challenge my knowledge. Challenge my
sitting on the couch Saturdays watching
these games processing
>> through smoothlytics.
>> Who can take it to the next level? All
right. who is not just a college player,
who is a pro player. And not just a pro.
I'm talking about a longstanding pro.
Yeah. See, that's the difference in my
when I look at it and say, "Here go a
player." This going to be a longterm
player. I'm not saying he'll a pro
bowler, right?
>> But he going to be a 10-year player,
right? And that's the difference in
them. And everybody thinks they a draft
guru. So, I'm poking at him,
>> right? I'm poking at them cuz everybody
think they know especially if they got
any like like if they know the player I
know his dad or watched him play at
Virginia Tech and watch him play high
school they think they know this is the
next one.
>> I don't know all the time. Just like
Logan strikes out.
>> See, I was just going to say this. I
imagine Logan looking at tape and being
like, "All right, he's long, athletic,
great ball skills.
>> Yeah,
>> quick twitch muscles." And you're like,
>> "He can this dude can play."
>> Yeah. He can overdo it. Like he can get
too analytical where it's mine is a
mixture. Eye test.
>> Okay.
>> Uh measurements,
>> right?
>> All right. Speed. All right. Everything.
I put it all in one jumbo and say, "All
right, what's the personal?" And I tried
to figure out the personality of a
player. And see, that's what people I
think don't take into consideration.
>> I mean, that's massive, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Because once you in the locker
room with 52 OTHER ALPHAS,
>> HOW'S YOUR personality gonna match with
52 other alphas?
>> Right?
>> And some people it's TOO MUCH CUZ THEY
ALWAYS BEEN THE ALPHA. THEY'VE always
been the dude. And now you're in a
locker room and they looking at you like
you've done nothing. See, that's what
people don't understand about you as a
rookie. It's called a clean slate
protocol. Everything that you've done in
high school and college is irrelevant
>> because everyone else has done that.
>> Done. It ain't nothing you can say in
this locker room, right? Yeah, man. I
would scored five touchdowns in a game.
Me, too. Like, it's it it's like it's
never going to be this independent thing
where you f to wow people, right? It's
going to be how can I take my skill set,
>> my knowledge, and take it to the next
level. No, you hear that from time to
time. Like a dude is crazy talented, but
then he also does an interview and the
scouts come away blown away by that
mentality.
>> By that mentality like that never give
up. If I don't know know it now, I know
it then. I figure it out. So, it's
mostly problem solving. Like, cuz most
of these guys been top tier athletes,
they ain't never had to problem solve.
>> They ain't never had to fix a situation.
Think about it. If you Texas, if you
Ricky Williams,
>> okay,
>> the first time you probably ran into
problems was the NFL.
>> No question. You
>> remember he would do the interviews with
his helmet on?
>> With his helmet on
>> because he had anxiety issues and didn't
like the attendance. He just wear his
helmet with the shield on.
>> With a shield on.
>> Yeah. There go see there go the anxiety.
Nobody knew he had anxiety but the
people inside. All right. So there go
the differences. All right. Did it take
him time to to grow out of that? It did
in New Orleans. By the time he made it
to the Dolphins,
>> he was on. Unbelievable.
>> So there go there go the little things
about that draft process.
>> So let's talk needs in the NFC East. So
we're going to talk about commanders
needs coming up in the draft. Let's
start with the hated Dallas Cowboys.
>> Hated.
>> So according to this article we read
that Anna was so kind to look up and
here by the way.
>> Hi everybody. Just jumping in. Just
jumping in. I was going to say this is a
headline segment. So we're going to go
through some headlines we read this
week. Thought were interesting. Yeah.
And that's why we're talking NFC East
needs. This is a good shot of you, Anna.
It looks like you're just chilling.
>> I'm hanging out in my fan cave.
>> Yeah, most definitely. It's good. I like
it.
>> Look like it smells like oak in there.
>> It does.
>> Yeah. Frank walked in the other day.
He's like, I can just smell it in here.
And I'm like, I it smells like nothing.
It's brand new.
>> No. No. I know it, but as an older
person, we're used to these panelings.
>> You know what's crazy? I What this
reminds me of, and it's blowing my mind,
is that I remember when I was like five
or six, cuz I was born early '7s, right?
And I remember I would come home. My dad
would take me home
>> during his lunch break.
>> And he was working on paneling the whole
living room. This exactly. And I
remember him putting up like the glue
and then the panel and he panled our
whole living room.
>> And it smelled like just like this.
>> Yes. You got to be old to understand.
>> Oh my god. The truth though.
>> So we start with the Cowboys biggest
needs. Middle linebacker. They need help
all over the defense honestly. Not
listen to me. I'm going to be honest
right now. I usually don't get old Jera
his props.
>> Mhm.
>> He is slowly putting together
a very good roster.
>> Like you look at this defense with Over
Sean like who just came back last year
who I think is a dog.
>> Texas boy.
>> All right. Over. You got Quinn Williams
in the middle. All right. Like you got
dudes. All right. You got Reale, Siobhan
Rale, who I think gonna be a hell of a
quarterback.
>> They have dudes. The question is,
>> can they put it all together? Cuz this
is what seems to be the Cowboys problem.
>> When the defense is good, the offense
stinks. When the offense is good, the
defense
>> Cuz last year, Dak was balling out.
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> Very. But the defense couldn't stop.
>> THE DEFENSE DIDN'T STOP NOBODY. NOW, I
GOT A FEELING the defense going to be
good this year,
>> right? AND THEY GONNA SNEAK ON OFFENSE.
LIKE IT just they can never sync it up.
But this is what I will say.
>> Okay,
>> all four rosters in the NFC East are
good rosters. All right, all of them.
And usually when the NFC, all four teams
are good. Somebody's going to represent
the NFC, the NFC as a whole in the Super
Bowl.
>> Yeah,
>> I say that every time. Think about it.
>> Think so.
>> All right. When we won the Super Bowls,
>> okay,
>> the Giants were good. The Cowboys was
good. The Eagles were
>> Everyone was good at some like
>> Yes.
>> the the competition was wild.
>> All right. When the Giants won, we was
all good.
>> Nobody great, but all us was good. Like,
it's just one of them things. We beat on
each other to go beat up everybody else.
>> Correct.
>> And I think this is one of those years
like I'm saying it right now.
Super Bowl representative is coming out
of NFC East.
>> Oh, clip that off. It ain't but four
options.
>> They feel it. They didn't had they feel.
I'm through with them.
>> Is the Michael Parson's trade once the
dust is settled because I think a lot of
people, myself included, thought Green
Bay got away with it here. But I think
in hindsight, the Cowboys did better
than people realized.
>> They did way better. It's It's that
Hershel Walker trade. You
>> That's the Oh my god.
>> You You remember everybody was like,
"Oh, I can't believe they traded
Hershel." And I like I don't think he's
that good anyway. All right. But they
was blown away with everything the
Cowboys got. Football, if you going to
always say this is about the football
team, not the football player.
>> I have never seen one top tier player go
win a Super Bowl, but I have seen a lot
of B players go win a Super Bowl.
>> All right. So, it's just one of them
things. One player, this not basketball,
right? This not basketball. One player
cannot change a team.
>> Quarterback maybe, but you still got to
have offensive line, right? got to still
have wide receivers. All right. So
that's why to me, as good as Green Bay
could be, Cowboys to me always going to
win that because they still got two
draft picks to to to pick from and then
all the players they got back then they
still end up some way getting Rashawn
Garry out of that.
>> Like how did that happen? So no, Green
Bay felt like they won. Cowboys want it.
>> Giants, according to this article, they
need right guard as their biggest need,
which you got to protect your
quarterback. Also, they need help on the
defense. They were awful against the
run, which is crazy to think about when
you think about that defensive line, but
they couldn't stop anybody.
>> Sexy Dexi had a terrible year last year.
Let's be honest. Uh Kavon Tibido, they
going to have to go and say it. He's a
bust.
>> You have that one game you're like, "All
right, all right."
>> No, he has the one game against us,
>> right? And then that's it. All right.
That's it. Brian Burns is a is an
animal.
>> Now that guy could be
>> He's an animal.
>> Then you draft like they got dudes.
>> Yeah.
>> And the one thing about Hobbar, he's
going to get the best out of them.
That's something that I feel like the
last coaching staff did not do. So he's
going to get the best out of them. The
question is,
>> who really is Jackson Dart?
>> I think Jackson's a player.
>> Listen,
>> I think he's a player.
>> Is Mississippi stamped and approved? ALL
RIGHT.
CAN HE reel in the bad plays?
>> That's the question. Because he kind of
plays outside of this
>> this box. Can you get him to play inside
the box and and and take care of the
ball
>> and he needs to take care of himself,
too?
>> Listen, he has to learn that the NFL is
not for the fate of
>> the I these kids, man. And I get it. I
get it. But at some point, you have to
realize if you want to preserve your
time and preserve your body and play a
long time in the league, especially at
quarterback,
>> it's hitters out here, man.
>> Yeah, you got to slide.
>> It's hitters out here. All right. But
that roster, when you look at that
roster, they got a number one receiver.
They got Scataboo in the back field. Uh
they just signed a tight end in free
agency. All right. With with Isaiah
likely. All right. They have plugged
some holes that they thought they had.
>> And Harbaugh will immediately make them
better.
>> He'll immediately make them better.
>> Okay. Eagles edge rusher because they
have had these super rosters. Now
they're getting to the point where they
can't pay everybody.
>> All right. You got two corners you going
to have to pay. All right. You just paid
one of your detackers. Jaylen Carter,
you're not going to be able to pay. Like
they're starting to peel.
>> And that's what good teams do.
>> And they're losing, dude.
>> They're starting to peel.
>> Kobe Dean's gone. That's what I'm
saying. It soon it might be a AJ Brown
departure.
>> I mean, he has to leave, right?
>> Listen, he has to.
>> But if any team can prevail
under disturbance, it's the Philadelphia
Eagles. That's their brand. We're going
to win, but we're going to do it our way
with bickering along the way from our
fan base, from the locker room, from the
city. Do y'all remember that interview
that the guy did that had just saved a
kid that they dropped the kid out of the
building and he caught it?
>> Yeah.
>> And they doing an interview with this
guy at the peak moment of his life. How
do you feel catching this child and
saving his child and that Philadelphia
dude stand up there and say, "You know
what? It felt good, but at least ain't
agar." LIKE THAT'S HOW SERIOUS THEY ARE.
THIS IS AT THE PINNACLE of this man's
CAREER. LIKE YOU JUST SAVED the person
and all he can think on his mind is act
like dropping the ball. That's all he
can think. That sums up Philadelphia as
a whole. They
do well under chaos. Everybody's not
like that. Every fan base, every city is
not like that. Philadelphia is chaos
personified.
>> Yeah.
>> And they got to have somebody in the
locker room keeping up chaos. If you
remember, let's turn the page back to
when I was playing. TO0 was that chaos
doing situps to drive in the driveway
was one man chaos.
>> One man they got to the Super Bowl. All
right. Like that's what Philadelphia is
as a city man. So edge rushers I think
they do need uh
the the big question is is Devonte Smith
a number one? If you're going to trade
AJ Brown
>> Yeah.
>> is Devonte Smith a true number one. You
got Dallas Goddard back. You got still
got Saquon Barkley. You still got one of
the best offensive lines in the
football. And who is Jaylen Herz? That's
gonna be the real.
>> I feel like Devonte is the perfect
number two. At least that's the way I
kind of see it.
>> I feel you. I think
>> like he has all the skills, but he's he
can explode as a number two. I wonder
how productive he would be as the
designated wide receiver one.
>> All right. Can I ask you this?
>> Yeah. Did you consider Tori Holt a
number two? The greatest show on turf
with Isaac Bruce.
>> That's what I was thinking of Isaac. I
consider Tori number one.
>> I could I consider Tori a number one?
>> Yeah.
>> So it is a theme where you can have two
number ones.
>> That's true. Very true.
>> All right. So
>> Well, the question like you were saying
is is Jaylen
>> Jayen Herz. Yeah.
>> There go the big story right there.
>> I I just don't know. like he has these
games that blow you away in the Super
Bowl, but then in the regular season,
>> you're down his accuracy.
>> You're down his can he throw the guy
open.
>> So, it's a big thing right there when
you talk Philadelphia is is this roster
starting to peel like an onion?
>> And I think it's starting to peel like
an onion right now.
>> Well, what's interesting to me is that
there was supposed to be a vote or
people expected maybe a vote on the tush
push this year.
>> Yeah.
>> Didn't happen.
>> Nobody cared.
>> Teams don't care anymore and they're
like, "We're not worried about you
anymore. We're not worried about your
tush pushing, right? Because remember a
year ago it almost got banned
>> this year.
>> This year nobody even brought it up.
>> It was the ugliest play in the NFL. It
was bad. Nobody like it was fans like
I'm tired of seeing it. Like it's a
rugby scrum.
>> Plus the referees can't call it right.
>> They can they started to
>> and then it got bad where the Eagles
were jumping every single time and the
referees
>> so they stopped running it. So there go
the thing about it. Can you enforce it?
and the referees found a way to enforce
it. Once they enforced it, it it's not a
lethal weapon anymore. So now come back
to the rest of us,
>> right? That mean your third downh
percentage goes down.
>> That's right.
>> And if your third down percentage 80%
and it goes to 50, that's a ton. That's
a ton. That's a lot of games lost.
>> Burgundy go. Yeah. Let's talk
commanders.
>> Yeah.
>> Receiver is the biggest need.
>> We got a room full of receivers. All
right. Trayon Bur I am very high on.
>> Isn't he the secret guy that the secret
guy but you know what I mean? The guy
that we're not the rest of the league
isn't looking at but who could actually
have a breakout year.
>> Former firstrounder who finally found
his tracking.
>> Mhm.
>> All right. See, I always tell people
every great Super Bowl team got at least
two former first rounders who didn't pan
out in their first spot.
>> Like that's how you steal right there.
That's how you steal a draft pick right
there. You got Trayon Burks, you got
Terry Mcloin. Don't forget a a healthy
offseason with Terry and then Trayon
Burks getting an off season with Jedi 5.
That changes everything. All right. I
just think AP did such a good job
>> of filling all the rooms that you had to
look and say which the weakest room and
you gonna pick wide receiver. But you
never know that until the season start.
People didn't think highly of Zakius,
but since he left here, he been getting
paid.
>> Yeah.
>> Like that's just what it is. Until you
do it, the NFL won't give you the luxury
of saying you might. Well, I'm saying
Trayon Burks might be the perfect 1B to
Terry Mclo.
>> How impressive was Van last week, by the
way.
>> I I enjoyed Van.
>> I loved Van.
>> You can always You can always kind of
tell second generation footballers
because like Bluefoot, Sean Springs, his
daddy played for the Dallas Cowboys.
They have this era aura about them. He
walked in. I was like, just impressive.
>> Just impressive. Been here, done that
type of dudes.
>> I kind of wonder if it's also like that
veteran aura where it's like you you
know your game, you know what you can
bring to the team, you know where you're
going to fit. Like I just felt like he
so knew what he was doing. I think that
was also
>> I also think it's a father prepping.
Like if your father played in the NFL,
it's a prepping that preps you to get to
the NFL.
>> So you're ready for interviews. You
you're ready for the big show. You're
just ready because
>> nothing surprises you.
>> NOTHING SURPRIS CUZ YOUR POPS HAVE
already made it to the point where he's
telling you
>> that ain't what you think it is. All
right. This is what it is. I can always
tell when I'm around second generation
footballers. Also, speaking of
generational, I did not realize this.
This story came out a couple days ago.
Daryl Green.
>> Oh, my fault.
>> You and
D. Green. He tried out for Team USA, the
flag football team.
>> Yeah.
>> Unbelievable.
>> At 193 years old.
>> Unbeliev
And I think they should put this in the
Olympics. The old people 100 yard dash.
>> He's 66.
>> Yes. In every country, you send your
oldest, fastest dude.
>> Your oldest, fastest guy.
>> And I'm telling you, Dale Green will
beat everybody
over 50 years old in the world.
>> I believe that.
>> In racing right now, he's the fastest
old person on the planet. I'm telling
you this now. He'll beat everybody from
Africa, everybody from Australia,
everybody from Europe, everybody.
Period. We should put old people 100yard
race into the Olympics.
>> So Daryl Green is the fastest 66 year
old in the world probably right now.
>> He's the oldest over 50.
>> Yeah,
>> he's the oldest guy.
>> You think over 50? I don't I don't know.
>> He'll beat a 50-y old.
>> You think he beat Okay.
>> Yes, he
>> the fastest 50.
>> He beat me at 20. Listen, I was 21.
>> I say, you know,
>> I was at I was 21. Champ was 202 or 23
and we had the fastest [__] race. It
came down to his last three. He smoked
us.
>> I bet. And he was
>> no shame.
>> And he was 40.
He's just fast, man. I'm sorry. He just
he fast. And plus, he didn't get a lot
of injuries.
>> Oh, he was always,
>> but he was always available. So, when
you when you didn't get a lot of
injuries and you took care of your body,
>> yes. I I would say right now the fastest
guy
>> in the world over 50, nobody could touch
you. So, yay or nay?
>> Yeah.
>> When it comes to the draft, Washington
is going to trade down from seven.
>> I say nay.
>> Unless
Simpson, the quarterback,
>> Kai Simpson from uh Alabama
>> and somebody wants him.
>> If somebody wants him is the only way. I
don't see any other player that can
press the draft and change the draft. So
I ain't I'm saying nay because I don't
think anybody going to want seven from
us,
>> right?
>> That's the key. Do somebody want what
player can swing the pendulum besides
Sunonny Styles to make somebody come up
at seven besides Tai Simpson a
quarterback? So if Ty Simpson blows his
workouts away,
>> Yeah.
>> and somebody wants him inside the top
10, that's the only way. Like let's just
say the Jets want to get back in the top
10 at the at the number two.
>> Okay. take an RV or Reese and they like,
"Yeah, we want to let's go and get back
in here."
>> That's the only way. That's why I say
nay because it ain't enough quarterbacks
to move the pendulum.
>> I agree with you and I also think that
look, this team clearly has a lot of
needs even after free agency and there's
a lot of talent that they can use
amongst those top seven picks.
>> Yeah.
>> But I've also heard and I think it was
Logan that said this, that once you get
to like, you know, 10 to 24 that the
talent evens out a lot.
>> Yeah. It drops.
>> It drops quite a bit. Yeah.
>> So, it's sort of topheavy in the first
round. So, if they can get a lot of
picks like you're talking about and drop
down, that's the one thing. But I I
would say nay, too.
>> Yeah. I got to say nay on that one.
>> Okay. So, the current position group
with the least amount of depth is the
secondary.
>> LIES.
>> LIES. All right. They say in church,
lies. All right. No, I think the
defensive backfield is way deeper than
people think. We had a lot of injuries
last year. Trey Amos gets to go a whole
off seasonason get his body good. Mikey
Sand still another year of getting
better. Then you add a Nick Cross to it.
I think people forgetting about Will
Harris. Now Quan Martin can play a
little bit nickel, a little bit safety,
a little bit of this, a little bit of
that. Like so all I'm saying is it's
it's deeper than you think. And I know
people look at the rise and say, "I
think the edge rushers got all the
depth." Yeah, we got tons of depth at
the edge rusher. Tons of depth.
>> That was good. That was your good dorky
white guy voice. Yeah,
>> I believe all the edge rushers have the
depth.
>> Yeah, they they believe it. They got the
depth. But I would say the defensive
back has tons of depth.
>> Maybe I had to go back to the wide
receiver room and say we got more depth
than the wide receivers.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> How about this? Thoughts on the needs
for wide receiver? Rec
>> receiver, corner, and center. Okay. So,
you got Donte Jones as the new obviously
the defensive coordinator. Yeah. Last
year with the Vikings, I mean, he was
unbelievable. As part of that Vikings
defensive staff, the Vikings allowed
19.6 points per game, seventh best in
the NFL. They had the second best
passing defense. So, based on all of
that and you think about what this team
needs,
>> do you think they need to go more
defense? Do you think they swing to the
offense because of what they did in free
agency?
>> I just think it's best player available.
And I and you know you hear us use that
cliche all the time, but I think for
what we did free agency, it's the best
player available. All right, let's just
say Jeremiah Love is at seven. You're
taking him.
>> You have to.
>> Sunny Styles at seven. You're taking
him.
>> You're taking him.
>> All right, David Bailey at seven. You're
taking him. All right. I'm such a big
Kenyan Sadi fan. If if the other all THE
REST OF THE GUYS ARE GONE, HELL, I'M
TAKING HIM IN, TOO.
>> I'LL GIVE YOU CREDIT, TOO, because
you've been talking about this cat for
weeks. And since then, he's been moving
up the draft boards. People said, "This
is an athletic freak."
>> Yeah. Because he went to the combine
>> and blew people away.
>> Showed him what I've been seeing on film
all year. I'm looking at this dude like
he don't
>> I need you to jump off the screen to me.
>> Yeah.
>> Meaning, if you around all these college
players, I need you to look like you're
not one of those. When I watch Ken
Sadiko on the field, I'm like, he's not
one of those kids. This is a grown man.
He should not be out there, right? All
right. He looks the part. He is the
part. I'm just telling you, I know
that's too high for somebody, for most
people, for a tight end. Yeah. Seven.
>> But if all the other freakish athletes
are gone, and when I say freakish, RVL
Reese, Sunonny Styles, Jeremiah Love,
these are they are freaks.
>> Mhm.
>> There's one left and that's him. And I
want him. So, yay or nay? Washington's
free agency grade is a B. That's kind of
been the consensus across the NFL.
>> I give it a A.
>> Yeah.
>> Because they didn't go out, we didn't go
out and spend like 200 million on one
player.
>> Mhm.
>> We went out there and spent money and
still with money to to spend. And we got
>> a feel we almost feel the roster. We got
younger. We got faster. We got stronger.
We got longer. All right. We got edge
rushes.
Everything we went in with a weakness at
in free agency, we came out. It's a
strength.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I give it a A minus right now. And
you don't you really can't get a grade
Jinx into the season
>> because it's not even there's still
moves to be made.
>> Yeah. So, it's incomplete. You don't got
incomplete on the poor card. I never
did.
>> No.
>> Yeah. But incomplete.
>> Did you get excessive talking?
>> All right. I did uh this is what I got.
>> Okay. I became what they call the
teacher's pet.
>> No way.
>> Because
>> No. No. No way.
>> And I I had to sit next to her desk.
Like they had to remove me from right
with the rest of the class to make sure
class could operate.
>> All right. So I was always forced to sit
by the teacher. So I just started to
talk to them the whole time.
>> Yeah.
>> So the class loved it because now they
doing no teaching. They talking to me
the whole time. So that's what I was I
was a I was an interrupter because one I
would finish so quick.
>> Yeah.
>> Like you give me something to do, I'mma
finish it. And now here go the problem
cuz now I'm just sitting around
and it's too quiet. So now I'mma mess
with my homeboy over here talking a
little trash over here. They be like,
"No, get up. Go to the gym." I was
already told to go to the gym.
>> Mhm.
>> Uh come sit beside me. Uh just get out
of class. I used to get away with murder
because I compete I was such a nerd in
high school because I competed in all of
these called UIL University
Intercolastic League. So these are
>> they're school sanctioned but all these
competitions right from one act play to
typing to calculator to science. So I'd
be in English class and my teacher be
like, "You know what? Don't worry about
doing any work here. Just go to the
auditorium and practice your duet
acting." So me and my buddy have a whole
auditorium to ourselves.
>> Yeah. and she would just match my grade
to the highest grade in the class.
>> Yeah.
>> I had
>> computer science. Same thing.
>> Work on the calculator on the back.
>> Yeah.
>> I'll just match your grade with the
highest in the class.
>> It sound like
>> I had it happen in three different
classes cuz I'd already established
myself as someone who like already made
good grades. It's like don't worry about
it.
>> When you vote when you voted most likely
to succeed cuz I was I was best all
around.
>> See, I was voted most likely to succeed.
Class favorite. I was like pretty much
all of because I was like a athlete that
happened to like be funny.
>> Oh yeah.
>> So I didn't take myself very seriously.
>> So now that I opened back my yearbook
and I was like darn it, they got it
right. I I DID SUCCEED
BECAUSE BECAUSE WHEN YOU VOTED CUZ when
you voted these things, you don't really
take attention to it. But these are
grown-ups saying I don't know y'all. He
probably going to make it. Like he did
it. Like that what I'm saying? Like for
them to get it right like that. I was
like, you know what? I'm so proud OF MY
TEACHERS. I I HAD A GOOD GROUP of
teachers that Miss Hatchet and rest of
them that understood that he got what
it's take. He got charisma. He's He's
athletic.
>> He's looker. He's going to make He's a
looker.
>> Fred Smoot's a looker.
>> He's a looker. He's going to make it.
And when I when I when I when I go
through the the the the book, it's just
me smiling everything. Then I'm on every
page. football, basketball, baseball,
track, everything. Like even sports I
ain't even play. Tennis, I'm on their
picture.
>> Just dare
>> in the background.
>> YEAH, JUST THERE.
>> OH MY GOD.
>> SO, YES. SO, I I I do I enjoyed it.
>> The one award I got and I turned it down
cuz I hated it. Yeah. I also won most
organized. I'm like, that's nerdy. I
don't want that. I didn't show up.
You're
>> pretty organized. I'm pretty organized.
>> I watched you. You dress well.
>> You You kind of put together well. Yeah.
Your hair is always the same.
>> Thanks, man.
>> Yeah. So, you know,
>> appreciate you.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Appreciate you.
>> I think that was warranted. What about
you, Anna?
>> My junior year, I decided I would do
lacrosse. I'd never played before. I was
like really bad, but I had so much fun.
Like, I loved everybody on my team. I
had a great time. So, I got the
sportsmanship award and I was like,
>> a
>> that's a little pathetic, but thank you.
I was honored that they thought I had
good sportsmanship.
>> But see, that's that's the difference in
an athletes house. Like my kids know,
>> my brothers were like, "This is
embarrassing, Anna." But I
>> My kids know like my uh my son hit me up
like, "Yeah, dad, they had the quick
award show, but I left the award. I
threw it in the garbage." I like, "What
what award was it?" He was like, "Uh,
participate." He's like, "You you told
us never ever to bring them in the
house." And I like, "Yeah, cuz you
agreed to participate." Like when you
participate, you not get no trophy for
that. All right. You agreed to
participate. Every trophy that you get
need to be earned. You see them trophies
over there with the dust on it? I earned
every last one of them. All right.
>> We don't do participation.
>> In my sority, I got most likely to be
Tik Tok famous. I'm on a I'm on a
podcast now, though. So,
>> and Tik Tok.
>> You still have time.
>> Would you guys follow my Tik Tok if I
promote promoted my Tik Tok?
>> Started today. I'm sure not on Tik Tok.
So, I ain't got to change it.
>> This could be fun. I could do day in the
lives or something like
>> let's
>> let's make Anna Tik Tok famous.
>> Yeah. Okay. I'll let you guys know. I'll
keep you posted. That was really long
about me.
>> We got your back.
>> All right. Okay. Cool.
>> I would love that.
>> Next thing I know, I'm like
award saw that coming.
>> What? What a journey.
>> Okay. Yay or nay? Anna will become Tik
Tok famous.
>> Yay. in in this day and age with her
having this platform to boost her Tik
Tok.
>> I don't think these I don't feel like
our audience is Tik Tok audience though.
I don't think anybody here watches Tik
Tok.
>> Yeah, but you don't know it's some 20
year olds in there
>> watch. Yeah, maybe like it's it's a
difference now. Like the one thing about
podcasting and Tik Toking, once you like
THE MATCH,
>> IT'S ON FIRE.
>> YEAH, maybe I should start a Tik Tok. I
don't know what I really have no idea
what I would talk about. my job. Like
that's it.
>> Yeah.
>> Maybe living in DC.
>> A life.
>> Yeah.
>> A glimpse into the life of producer Ann.
>> So interesting.
>> No. No. No. It just You do it. You do a
Tik Tok from the humble heels of Denver.
>> Uhhuh.
>> To the metropolitan area. The DMV.
>> You're so right.
>> The transition.
>> You're right. You're right.
>> Let's think about it, Anna. You get
insight to the team, behind the scenes
stuff. You travel a lot.
>> You travel.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it'll be interesting.
>> Okay. Yeah, I'll start maybe for a week.
I'll try. I'll
>> Hey, I'll try again.
>> You'll be shocked how much money come
from.
>> Yeah, you're so right.
>> Yay or nay?
>> From Anna, too. Here, here's a good
transition from, you know, sweet.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, always nice person Anna to the
Raiders.
>> Raiders, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Silver and Black. Did they have the best
off season?
>> I think they got a lot done. I think
they got a lot done, especially
considering they got the number one
pick, the 33rd pick, the Yeah, I think
the Think about this. I'm going to paint
an offense for you. Fernando Mendoza
hands the ball off
>> to uh
>> Ashton.
>> Ashton Genty. Then he play actions to at
Genty and he throws to Brock Bowers, one
of the best, if not the best,
>> tight end in football.
>> And you add a wide receiver to that.
Oh yeah. The Raiders will not
be the old Raiders of the past.
>> Also, Linder Bomb is a great signing on
the line. Not sexy, who's a center, one
of the best centers. And that line has
to get better.
>> Yeah, they can't get worse,
>> right?
>> They was the worst offensive line I
think I have ever seen in my life. They
got better up front. They got better on
defense. They got better. And now they
going to get the number one quarterback
in the draft. Yeah. Yeah. The Las Vegas
Raiders
uh had the number one, two, or three
best off season so far. I agree.
>> And now Las Vegas trying to get a W. I
mean, to get a NBA team also. I hope
they do the expansion.
>> Oh my god.
>> They're going to cuz I want to see the
Seattle SE SuperSonics back there so
bad. I want to see them so bad in that
green and gold. They had one of the best
starter jackets of all time. All right.
>> All the green with the Sonics across.
>> Oh, yeah. With the city coming across
that thing. So, I want Seattle to get
their basketball team back. And Las
Vegas. I'm just wondering what the name
is going to be.
>> Can you imagine an NBA All-Star game
>> in Vegas
>> in Las Vegas?
>> That's Yeah.
>> I mean, forget it.
>> Yeah. No, this right now, the only hope
for Vegas to stay open as a city is
sports.
>> I hate to say it with with gambling
legal every state.
>> Yeah.
>> The only thing that can get you to go to
Vegas now is sports.
>> Final one. Kyler Murray to the Vikings.
Best signing of free agency. Yay.
>> It could be him. I like it.
>> And McConnell together. Think about
McConnell's offense cuz that's the star,
>> right? The pen and the paper. That's the
star. Now, when those plays he call
don't work, Kyler can make them work
with his legs. When them plays uh off
time or get broken up, Kyler can make
plays. This is Kyler's best play caller
that he's ever had.
>> Mhm.
>> This is Kyler's best Yeah. Cuz I love
DeAndre Hopsson, but he is not Justin
Jenkins Jefferson.
>> No.
>> No, he ain't.
>> That's the best weapons that he's had,
the best offensive line that Kyler's
had.
>> Y
>> Yeah. I think they going to be a
problem. I think they're going to be a
legit problem cuz I think people forget
that just two years ago, Kyler had
Arizona like 12-0. Mhm. Like people
forget that. Does he have a ceiling
though? Like I think he's a great sign.
Also, when you look at what they pay,
because Arizona is going to pay most of
that salary, so it's a great sign.
>> They're paying $1.5 million, right? And
like they said, we not bringing him in
for a one-year thing. They want him to
be Now, the only person that I feel
sorry for is JJ McCro.
>> I was just say, how quickly did they
sour on him?
>> JJ, you handsome.
You won a national championship.
You're basically the Bachelor now,
Jesse Plumb. better than the
Bachelorette.
>> No, no, I'm just saying you're basically
the Bachelor right now, Palmer. That's
who you are. Love it. Live it. I just
hope he get a second chance.
>> Yeah.
>> I hope he get a second chance because
the NFL will sour on the quarterback so
quickly. I hope he gets a second chance,
but I I do not see him that happening in
Minnesota. Cuz once that city sour on
you, they sour on you cuz they they a
harsh fan base.
>> Because I mean, you know.
>> Oh, I know. Yeah,
>> I know. I live there and watch them get
mad at us all the time. Put stuff in
your yard, all kind of stuff. And then I
thought to myself, why are they so
fickle? Then I realized they have never
won a championship.
>> That's right.
>> Like the whole state in no sport besides
baseball.
>> I was going to say the Twins. Yeah.
>> The Twins. But you talking about hockey?
>> The Wild.
>> Wild? No.
>> Never. The Timberwolves?
>> Nope.
>> Ever.
>> The Vikings? No. You talking about a fan
base? Oh, even the college team stinks.
They have no championships. Like none.
Like
>> that's true.
>> Like none.
>> And the thing is the crazy thing about
the Vikings is the Vikings go a long way
back.
>> NO, THEY WERE ONE OF THE the fixtures,
>> right? They had the purple people
leaders back in I mean they were really
good. They just couldn't get over the
hump. Like how could a whole entire
state never win in it that they won one
time and that's Prince.
>> They had the best artists. That's true.
Other than that, you're talking about a
state of people that just don't know
what winning feels like. And think about
them compared to a state like
Massachusetts, Boston that just
currently has parades for no damn
reason. Yeah.
>> All right. Yeah. Minnesota. Now I know
why y'all so filthical.
And the thing is, Kyler, this I this is
not a he'll come in for a year or two
and guide JJ. No, no, no, no, no. He's
the dude.
>> He's the dude there. They're going to do
everything they can to keep him back.
Keep him there. I just think they feel
so bad with the Sam Donald thing.
>> Yeah.
>> Sam Donald
>> made a huge mistake.
>> He could have won them the first
championship of I don't see too much
difference in that Minnesota team with
Sam Donald and that Seattle team with
Sam Donald. Both got great defenses.
Both can run the ball. both got number
one wide receivers. Sam could have
brought y'all y'all first ring and you
traded him. OH, YOU LET HIM GO. YEAH,
you let him go and now look at him.
Yeah. Now Sam just at Disney World. Sam
all over the place right now. Good for
him. Let's pay some bills real quick.
All right, let's do it. Man, I'm telling
you, I'm going to have to start wearing
glasses on this show. Did I say this
last time?
>> But but they they go to
>> I make the font larger.
>> No, it's fine. I Here's the thing. I can
see. It's like an aigmatism. You know
what I'm talking about? Where you can
see it, but it's just slightly like
>> I don't know. I got 2010 vision.
>> Well, you're most likely to succeed.
>> Yeah, I did. I read the bottom of the
line when I go get my check. For real.
Do you?
>> I can see through wood.
>> Commanders fans,
Segeek is the official primary ticketing
partner of Hail of the Commanders and
here to help you experience all of the
action from football to funk and any
other live events at Northwest Stadium.
SeatGeek has the tickets. Segeek is the
official primary ticketing partner of
the Washington Commanders and Northwest
Stadium. Plus, huddle up Commanders
fans. The Commanders Golden Pass raffle
operated by the Virginia Lottery gives
you the chance to win the ultimate fan
experience. That means tickets, the VIP
treatment, special appearances by
Washington Legends, and so much more.
Limited tickets are available. So go
online vaotter.com/commanders
to enter the raffle today. That is
vaottery.com/commanders
and break. And you know the command
center fans have put you in the reading
rainbow competition that we got, you
know, sponsored by Lavar Burton. Yes.
And they have put you in it and said
that you I'm in.
>> Yeah. And that it's a reading contest
because we we do our reads. me, Santana,
Logan, and we compete. We're football
players, so we compete in everything.
So, you know, I'm sponsored by
Mississippi State. You know, Logan's
sponsored by UCLA, Satana sponsored by
Miami, and now you sponsored by Texas
University. And now you're a part of the
group.
>> Let me see. Okay, here's here's the
comment.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. I listen and watch everything the
team does on social media. The reads
from Santana, Logan, and Fred are nice.
Nod for Tan Man, but of everyone there.
Jinx is number one all day. Appreciate
you. B Mitch close second. Fred is my
dude and always has me laughing, but
sometimes he tries too hard.
>> Thank you, Anna, by the way.
>> I was gonna say, round of applause for
Jinx.
>> Thank you, Anna. First of all, Jinx was
can't do it.
>> JINX JINX WAS A RED FLAG. I'm not going
to applaud that.
>> Red won't even raise a hand except to be
like, "All right, let's Jinx was a was a
a media prodigy coming out of school."
All right, it's safe to say, right? He
was immediately the the the the most
mediocre thing he could do is read like
like and on camera on time and he knows
like me how to put the emotion into the
reads cuz some reads will tell you read
this slow
>> uh emote emote on this.
>> Jinx already doge that. I'm not giving
Jinx props for something that he been
doing 40 years. I'm not. And Jinx like
me is part of what we call the
teleprompter boys. So true. If we
started in media reading teleprompterss.
So if you can read a teleprompter
>> Yeah.
>> a read is nothing.
>> That's very true.
>> So
>> yeah, I'm not going to
>> I thought Anna was going to say
something.
>> Oh, I was going to yawning. I've
decided. No, no, no. I was going to say
something, but I really caught myself
there. Oh, I was going to say um draft
party.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Thursday night, April 23rd, Northwest
Stadium. We may or may not be there. So
definitely come hang out. I think it's
going to be a really fun time.
>> It's awesome. And um I can't wait to see
what gets put together for that night. I
think it's going to be a great time. See
who we get at number seven or or trade
back or something happens. We don't
know.
>> Regardless, draft part is going to
happen no matter what.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I I had a lot of people talk trash
to me at the waterfront yesterday about
a draft party we had.
>> They did?
>> Yeah. Talking about I'm out there
selling lies at the draft party because
>> Okay. Yeah, we know. Okay.
>> Because because of who we drafted and I
was like Yeah. It's the best. And they
were like, "No, you was wrong."
>> Oh, I'm not even gonna say it.
>> AND THAT'S FINE. LIKE I SAY, CALL ME
OUT. I'M FINE. I CAN TAKE IT. I'M A BIG
BOY. RIGHT. THAT'S FINE. But that's
fine. Come call me out this year. All
right. That's what you do.
>> Before we go.
>> Yeah.
>> Anna put together this bracket. Best
number seven. You want to set it up,
Anna?
>> Oh, no. No. Please.
>> Best number seven draft picks of all
time. So, she took number seven picks
and then put them against each other.
So, we decide which player drafted
number seven was is the best.
>> All right, let's go.
>> Okay, here we go. First one,
>> Adrien Peterson.
>> Oh,
>> 2007, Ben Sul 2021.
>> I'm sorry. Adrien Peterson was born to
be a running back.
>> He sure was.
>> I'm sorry. When I first seen this dude
just body, I was like, "Oh my god, I got
to got to hit him." Then I played
against him and I'll never forget it.
They tossed him a sweep to my side and
he was running towards me and he was
galloping. So it was this up and down
thrush just galloping and I was like is
this dude a stallion of horses? Oh my
god, he can't this ain't this cannot be
his running style. And they did it
again. I was like he's just born to run
the ball. I'm sorry. Yeah,
>> the the speed combination, the strength
combination, the
he was God's gift to running back. And I
love me some Pino Su. I love Su.
>> Yeah.
>> Think he one of the best offensive line
in football,
>> but he ain't Trent WS. Right.
>> All right.
>> Well, but they still young enough where
he's got a long career.
>> That's so funny. Trent Williams and
Adrien Peterson was on the same team.
>> Huh? Monsters. All right. Adrien
Peterson born to be a running back. He
has no other job choice. You know how
you just Andre the Giant. You got one
job. You're a wrestler. You're a
wrestler. Like you cannot work at a shoe
store. You cannot be a truck driver. You
was born to wrestle. Adrien Peterson was
born to run the ball. When he was born,
it was a little football tucked in right
there. And And they knew it. This dude
right here is born to run the football.
>> What's the recruiting story back when he
went to Oklahoma that Bob Stoops because
Adrien Peterson's father was in prison?
>> Yes. And Bob Stoops went to jail to
visit Adrien Peterson's dad as part of
the recruitment process.
>> Yes. All right. Yes.
>> Whatever it takes. Whatever it takes.
>> Whatever it takes.
>> All right. I want to get your take on
this one for your take on this one. 1992
Troy Vincent,
>> Champ Bailey. 1999.
>> You know, I love me some Troy. Troy, my
dude. Me and Troy got the same barber.
You know what I'm saying? Troy is just
my dude. Troy just a good dude. Like one
of the most intelligent dudes you ever
gonna meet. But Champ Bailey is
something different.
>> Listen, my old teammate, my old running
mate, my left corner, I'm the right
corner. I love Champ to this day. That's
my dude. One of the best athletes I've
ever seen. I told people I have had the
luxury of being around probably five of
the top athletes in football of all
time.
>> Okay.
>> Champ, most definitely, two-way player,
wide receiver, uh, cornerback and return
kicks. One of the best. Lavar Arrington,
one of the most put together athletes
you will ever see in your life. Dion,
Dale Green, like I have had the Sean
Taylor. These are once ina-lifetime
athletes and Champ is a once in a uh
once in a lifetime athlete. Champ Bailey
over Troy Vincent. I don't think that
one was hard.
>> Yeah, Troy's very good, but Champ
Hallame. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Champ was great. It's it's a
difference.
>> Oh, here's a current player on the list.
Mike Evans 2014.
Sterling Sharp 1988.
>> I think kids don't know what Sterling
Sharp used to be.
>> I agree.
>> Sterling Sharp was unstoppable.
Like all I can remember every time I
watch a Green Bay game is him diving,
catching the ball, and burning somebody
for 70 yards. Sterling Sharp is one of
these unappreciated.
>> I'mma tell you what, wide receivers that
don't talk trash don't do themsel
justice.
>> Yeah.
>> Santana like that. So quiet. don't sell
themselves.
>> I start to say he didn't talk trash at
all. Right. No. Or very little.
>> No. No talk. But then they get mad at
the ones that do and they become
household names. Like that's the thing
about it. You can't be a sports car
without a loud motor. And that's what a
receiver is. It's a sports car. But but
then we got these sports cars that's
electric car. They don't sound apart.
>> Sterling Sharp was the first electric
sports car.
>> I Here's the thing about sir. I agree
with you. Sterling was amazing. And his
career is overlooked for two reasons.
Number one, because it was a shame.
>> Short. It Yeah.
>> And it was short, right? It was because
I had a neck injury. Couldn't play any
longer. And then, of course, his brother
comes along and not only is his brother
great, but he's very boisterous and
immediate. People forget
>> Sterling could play. I I would probably
still give it to MIKE EVANS, THOUGH.
>> I'M GIVING IT TO MIKE.
>> BUT I we got to give Sterling his I want
to give Sterling his flowers because it
was just deserved. He a Hall of Famer. I
think Mike Evans Mike Evans is a shoe in
for the Hall of Fame. Most definitely. I
just think Mike Evans, man, 10 seasons,
over a thousand yards, he's been a
menace. Like Mike Evans has been a
menace. And when I say unstoppable at
his size, he reminds me of not quite,
but Calvin Johnson. Megatron. Let me
tell you something about Megatron.
>> His physical,
he's just
>> 66,
230 lb wide receiver. I remember
standing up beside him like, "So this me
and him? This is what's going on? I
supposed to stop him?" If
>> I lined up across from a receiver that
big and that fast, oh my god.
>> It got to the point, I have never seen
the NFL stoop this low. It got to a
point where, you know, they put two guys
out there for a gunner on punt team,
they start to put two corners out there
>> on regular plays. Ain't no receiver
ever, not Jerry Rice, not Randy Moss,
not Terrell Owens ever, garnered that
attention. Like, you know what? The only
way we're gonna stop him is put two
dudes. Usually we double team like the
corner up here, the safety back here
waiting on him. No, they said, you know
what? Both of y'all just get right over
there and let's just let's just deter
the quarterback from even throwing it.
Matthew Stafford still feeding him.
Yeah.
>> Just feeding him like and and Mike Evans
has that type of aura to his game.
>> Yeah, no doubt about it, man. and he's
not done yet. And I loved when he broke
that receiving record last year, got
1,000 yards again and his team just
rushed him. That tells you that tells
you the respect right there.
>> The respect of it. And that tells you
that the he ain't bigger than the locker
room. And we we we pride guys that ain't
bigger than the locker room. That's why
Tom Brady has always been one of his
play any of his teammates, they always
say that's their favorite guy because if
you good and don't take yourself too
serious, that says everything to a
locker room.
>> Finally.
This is fun. Josh Allen in 2018. Josh
Hines Allen 2019.
>> JOSH ALLEN AND JOSH ALLEN. YOU KNOW, HE
CHANGED HIS name to Hines Allen because
people kept getting him mixed up with
Josh Allen. One is black and one is
white, right?
>> But he was just tired of it. So he was
like,
>> I'm going to put my uh my mom's name on
on on the front of my name. So now it's
Hans Allen.
>> But this Josh Allen. This is a long This
is years ago when I was coming up the
escalator on the metro.
>> Yeah.
>> And I hear a guy go, "Hey, Fox 5
weather." And I was like, "Yeah, it's
going to be A GOOD ONE TODAY."
>> KNOWING YOU AIN'T SAYING nail day.
>> I've never done weather in my life.
>> AND THAT'S WHY I PUT NO EFFORT into
correcting it. Like I put no effort in
correcting people BECAUSE
>> I 72 TODAY. ENJOY.
>> YEAH. I'm just putting no effort in
correcting people. Whatever you think is
fine. It's fine with me, right? I've
been called all kind of football players
name. Like all kind of it it doesn't
bother me, right? I was at WGN the other
day and I'm in the vegetables I mean the
fruit section picking out, you know, I
love my fruit.
>> Somebody holl out, Michael B. Jordan.
>> NO, STOP IT.
>> STOP IT. I'M not doing this today.
>> I was like, no way. So I turned around.
I turned around.
>> Oh, I'm so sick of like Mike B, what you
DOING IN HERE?
OKAY, NEXT ROUND. Next round. And then
Okay. Okay. Adrien Peterson or Mike
Evans.
>> Oh, we're going. Oh, I did not realize
we were moving on.
>> Yep.
>> Okay.
>> Next round.
>> Adrien Peterson or Mike Evans?
>> Adrien Peterson.
>> I think it's AP. Okay.
>> It's AP.
>> Okay. Champ Bailey or Josh Allen?
>> Champ Bailey.
>> I gota go with the Hall of Fame and not
the guy that
>> I mean now potentially Josh, but right
now it's got to be Champ.
>> Oh, yeah. Champ.
>> Okay. Adrien Peterson or Champ Bailey.
I'm a cornerback. I gotta go Champ. I'm
sorry. Champ played offense a defense.
Peterson just played offense.
>> I'll go I'll go Peterson. You know what
though? He went Oklahoma. I hate
Oklahoma. Let's go Champ.
>> Oh, so Champ's the winner. Let's go. And
Washington drafted. It was fitting. Um
I'm going to say if we left anybody out,
you guys, please chime in. Who do you
think should have won the bracket?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I need to check out who's the
number seven pick in my draft. 01.
>> Let me look it up. That's a good
question because we had one of the best
drafts of all time. Number for one pick,
Michael Vic. All right.
>> Then we got guys like Leanian Thompson.
>> Oh, it was Andre Carter.
>> Dre Carter.
>> Yeah, he should have been in the He was
my like one of my Oh, I was going to put
>> Andre Carter. We had Richard Seymour. We
had Chad Johnson, Steve Smith, Reggie
Wayne, Santana Moss, David Terrell. Uh
>> you said Leaneian Tom. Oh yeah, we
deucemech Alistister.
>> It's a hell of a lot of talent.
>> When I say a draft, I mean a draft.
>> That's a draft. Okay guys, before we let
you go, don't forget draft party.
Northwest Stadium.
>> Circle your calendar.
>> Put it in your reminders, whatever it
is. April 23rd.
>> Come talk a little flack to me.
>> Yeah.
>> The the the draft guru ain't always
right.
>> Right.
>> I mean, we're talking to someone who's
most likely to succeed.
>> I was You was also voted that. Me and
you, not Anna.
>> Yeah, but we're making Anna Tik Tok.
>> Okay. Yeah, exactly. Priorities.
>> Most most Tik Tok friendly.
>> Yes.
>> I really loved Tik Tok in college. That
was my like thing.
>> Why did you get away from it, by the
way?
>> Oh, it's so addictive. I could sit on
there for hours.
>> That's true.
>> That was my problem. I I I get so
interested in things I could just
>> Did you ever get the message like, "Hey,
looks like you've been scrolling for a
while. Maybe take a break."
>> Oh. Oh, yeah. I had my neighbor I should
probably stop with how bad this is. I
had my neighbor put a password in for
like a time limit and one day I had a
really bad day and I knocked on her
door. I was like, "Payton, can you
please I had a bad day. Can you
>> just crackheaded? Could you please do I
had a problem?
>> I need to get
>> So that's why I'm hesitant. But fair.
>> Maybe I just like keep the app off my
phone and I'll just keep it on my iPad
or something."
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know. I don't have that
addiction because I don't do TikTok.
>> Yeah. Like,
>> yeah, don't start. Don't
>> My kids call me old because you on
Facebook. I like, "Is you gonna make you
a Facebook?" They like, "No, that's for
old people."
>> Like, do you know young kids do not
participate in Facebook?
>> That's crazy to me because that's how
you get your um high school graduation
invitations.
>> That's Facebook.
>> Yeah. I didn't have a Facebook and I had
to create one my senior year because
that's how you got invited to parties to
like your your graduation parties.
>> Oh my god.
>> I know.
>> What a world. We living in a techn
technical world that now the old
technology is played out. Yeah,
>> it's all about the new new. It's all
about the new new.
>> Well, that's going to do it for the Get
Live podcast presented by Segeek Anna
Smooth. I'm Jinx. Make sure you like,
subscribe, and tell us what you think in
the comments. Also, don't forget to keep
emailing us about Fred's mock draft
challenge. Mhm.
>> The Get Loud podcast was filmed at the
Big Bear AI Command Center Studios. Big
Bear AI offers mission ready AI for
rapidly evolving world and proudly
protecting the Washington Commanders and
his fans.
The views and opinions expressed by our
podcast guests andor hosts are their own
and do not necessarily reflect the views
or positions of the Washington
Commanders or any of their
representatives.